<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workgroups on Team Open</title>
    <link>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workgroups on Team Open</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://teamopen.org/workgroups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Workgroups</title>
      <link>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/about/</guid>
      <description>About workgroups Workgroups are responsible for particular tasks within our community. By letting them be autonomous and responsible for their respective tasks there are two main benefits:
 Authority can be more decentralized. Contributors can more easily help with the particular tasks they&amp;rsquo;re interested in.  Joining/leaving a workgroup Workgroups are open to anyone. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, you can join by creating a new issue using the &amp;ldquo;Join workgroups&amp;rdquo; issue template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workgroups</title>
      <link>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-lifeguard-devs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-lifeguard-devs/</guid>
      <description>Workgroup: Lifeguard Devs People who maintain OSS in the Lifeguard programe.
ID: wg-lifeguard-devs
Discord: #wg-lifeguard-devs
The Lifeguard Devs workgroup handles emergency maintenance of open-source projects, that are in the Lifeguard project. The overall work on the Lifeguard project is done in wg-lifeguard instead.
Join when you are interested in maintaining open-source projects in need.
Roles    Role Description     trial New workgroup members who are in a trial period with limited permissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workgroups</title>
      <link>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-lifeguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-lifeguard/</guid>
      <description>Workgroup: Lifeguard Development of the Lifeguard project itself.
ID: wg-lifeguard
Discord: #wg-lifeguard
The Lifeguard workgroup works on Team Open&amp;rsquo;s Lifeguard project. This workgroup focusses on the overal project, it is separate from wg-lifeguard-devs, which is the workgroup that handles emergency maintenance of open-source projects.
Join when you are interested in developing the Lifeguard project.
Roles    Role Description     trial New workgroup members who are in a trial period with limited permissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workgroups</title>
      <link>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-media/</guid>
      <description>Workgroup: Media (Social) media, publication and communication tasks.
ID: wg-media
Discord: #wg-media
The Media workgroup handles (social) media, publication and communication tasks. They manage announcements, blog posts, social media accounts and makes sure we communicate these well internally and externally.
Join when you are interested in how Team Open communicates.
Roles    Role Description     trial New workgroup members who are in a trial period with limited permissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workgroups</title>
      <link>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-organization/</guid>
      <description>Workgroup: Organization Organization level day-to-day tasks.
ID: wg-organization
Discord: #wg-organization
Organization level day-to-day tasks.
Join when you are interested in how Team Open organizes itself.
Roles    Role Description     trial New workgroup members who are in a trial period with limited permissions.   credentials People who handle login details / credentials for any part of the organization and share it with the appropriate other workgroups and members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workgroups</title>
      <link>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teamopen.org/workgroups/wg-outreach/</guid>
      <description>Workgroup: Outreach Reaching out to places and people where Team Open may be of help.
ID: wg-outreach
Discord: #wg-outreach
The Outreach workgroup looks for places where Team Open may offer help, or people that may be interested in joining us and contacts them.
Join when you are interested in connecting with the larger community.
Roles    Role Description     trial New workgroup members who are in a trial period with limited permissions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>